http://www.boavida.net/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
PRIVACY POLICYIDENTIFICATION INFORMATION OF THE RESPONSIBLE FOR TREATMENTRegistered Name
BOAVIDA, SL
VAT
ESB43495936Address:
C/ Lluís Companys i Jover, 3, 43330 Riudoms, SpainGENERAL PRIVACY INFORMATION.Through this website, personal data of users is not collected without their knowledge, nor are they transferred to third parties. In order to provide the best service and in order to facilitate the use, the number of pages visited, the number of visits, as well as the activity of visitors and their frequency of use are analyzed. For these purposes, Boavida SL, uses the statistical information developed by the Internet Service Provider.Boavida SL, does not use cookies to collect information from users, nor does it register access IP addresses. Only own, session cookies are used for technical purposes (those that allow the user to navigate through the website and use the different options and services that exist in it).SCOPEThis Privacy Policy of BOAVIDA, SL regulates the collection, use and other forms of processing of personal data provided by users on this website or in any of the Internet environments of BOAVIDA, SL.By means of the implementation of the forms included in the different websites, regarding services provided by BOAVIDA, SL, Users accept the inclusion and treatment of the data they provide in the processing of personal data, of which BOAVIDA, SL is the owner. Can exercise the relevant rights as set forth in the following clauses.All legal texts are available to users and / or interested in the corresponding website.Who is responsible for the processing of your data?BOAVIDA, SL, is the legal entity responsible for collecting and processing your personal data in relation to the services it provides.BOAVIDA, SL is committed to respect and safeguard your privacy and the security of your data. The treatment manager identifying details are:Responsible
Business Name
BOAVIDA, SLVAT
ESB43495936Address: C/ Lluís Companys i Jover, 3, 43330 Riudoms, Spain CONTACT EMAIL: info@boavida.netWith what purpose do we collect your data?As arranged in the current regulation, BOAVIDA, SL only collects the data strictly necessary to offer the services derived from its activity and other services, management and activities attributed by the Law.In this website, only contact information, provided by Users, is processed.The data collected from the user will be treated with the purposes of:•	Management of contact data.•	Sending information that may be of interest to you.•	Management of candidates in selection processes.•	Customer Management.•	Management of potential clients.It is reported that automated evaluations will not be carried out, nor will user profiles be developed.Likewise, we inform you that the information of the databases can be used for the identification of the Users and for the realization of statistical studies of the registered Users.
How long do we keep your personal information?Personal data will be kept as long as the user does not state otherwise and for the legally established conservation periods, unless for logical and obvious reasons they have lost the usefulness or the legitimate purpose for which they were collected.To which recipients will your data be communicated?Personal data entered on the website will not be transferred to third parties (without the express consent of the Users, their personal data and / or navigation), except in cases covered by current legislation.In the rest of the cases, BOAVIDA, SL will collaborate so that third parties comply with current legislation, although the responsibility will be demandable to the aforementioned third parties.BOAVIDA, SL does not sell, rent or transfer the personal data of the users of this Website, except in the case that is necessary for the provision of the service itself.BOAVIDA, SL does not sell, rent or transfer the e-mails of its users to other companies, except when necessary for the service itself.The website has links, applications or functionalities shared with third parties, such as social networks or on-line communication systems, BOAVIDA, SL is not responsible for the information collected in these applications, functionalities or social networks owned by third parties as it hasn´t any management capacity or control over them, being therefore applicable the legal notices and privacy policies that may appear on the websites or similar third parties.What are the rights of Users who provide us with their data?Users may exercise, with respect to data collected in the manner described in the first point, the rights recognized in Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and the Council of April 27, 2016 relating to the protection of natural persons as regards the processing of personal data and the free circulation of these data and repealing Directive 95/46 / EC (General Data Protection Regulation), and in particular the rights of portability, access, rectification , suppression and limitation to treatment.The rights referred to in the preceding paragraph, may be exercised by each User by written and signed request, accompanied by a photocopy of ID or Passport, addressed to the following address:BOAVIDA, SLC/ Lluís Companys i Jover, 3, 43330 Riudoms, SpainLikewise, we inform users that they can withdraw their consent for the processing of their data at any time, as well as that they can submit a claim to the Control Authority (Spanish Data Protection Agency) if deemed appropriate.COMMUNICATION OF INCIDENTS AND IRREGULARITIESIn the case of any conduct or situation that could be susceptible to generate an incidence or irregularity of any kind, please contact:
BOAVIDA, SLC/ Lluís Companys i Jover, 3, 43330 Riudoms, SpainCOMMITMENT OF THE USER FOR IT’S DATA TO BE ENTERED IN A TREATMENTInserting the data in any or some of the data collection sheets implies accepting the present conditions of use and privacy policy, assuming that you have been informed of the conditions of use and legal notice thereof and that you agree to to its full compliance during browsing and participation in https://www.boavida.netIn any case, the user is responsible for the authenticity of the data provided, that are accurate, current and complete for the purpose they are provided, assuming responsibility for the damages, both for loss of profit as for emerging damage, which could be generated by said inaccuracies or falsehoods. In any case, if the data provided in the corresponding forms was the owner of a third party, the user is solely responsible for the correct capture of the consent and information to the third party on the aspects reflected in this legal notice and privacy policies.RESPONSIBILITY OF USERS FOR USE AND CONTENTBoth the access to the websites and the use that may be made of the information and contents included therein, shall be the sole responsibility of the person who carries it out. Therefore, the use that can be made of the information, images, content and / or products reviewed and accessible through it, will be subject to the legality, whether national or international, applicable, as well as the principles of good faith and lawful use by the Users, who will be entirely responsible for the access and correct use. The Users will be obliged to make a reasonable use of the services or contents, under the principle of good faith and with respect to current legislation, morals, public order, good customs, the rights of third parties or their own BOAVIDA, SL, all according to the possibilities and purposes for which they are conceived. BOAVIDA, SL does not assume responsibilities, whether direct or indirect, for emergent damage or loss of profit, derived from the misuse of the services or contents made by the Users or third parties.LSSI-CE INFORMATIONIn compliance with the duty of information contemplated in article 10 of the current Law 34/2002, of July 11, Services of the Information Society and Electronic Commerce, we inform you that the dynamizer and content management of the Web where you can download different applications and / or information is BOAVIDA, SL with address at 43330 Riudoms, C/ Lluís Companys i Jover, 3 and with the management of the Internet domain http://www.boavida.net registered in the corresponding registry, attending to communications from users and / or interested parties through the e-mail info@boavida.net.Any other commercial, administrative or contracting activity of goods and / or services is the responsibility of the company mentioned above, owner of this domain.INFORMATION ON THE USE OF OTHER WEBS AND SOCIAL NETWORKSBOAVIDA, SL is only responsible for the content and management of the web pages of which it is the owner or has a right of similar nature. Any other website or social network or repository of information on the Internet, outside of this website, is the responsibility of its legitimate owners.BOAVIDA, SL collaborates in an ordinary way with different applications and Web environments, and always recommends that all users before accessing these web environments carefully read the corresponding legal notices and privacy policies, and only access them once they have understood and accepted in its entirety legal text.BOAVIDA, SL is committed to control the contents that are exposed in these social networks and will expel those users who make an incorrect use in them.BOAVIDA, SL recommends, following instructions from the National Institute of Communication Technologies (INTECO) and the Spanish Agency for Data Protection (AEPD), for the use of social networks or navigation in Web environments, the execution of the following actions ( in case one day is available for use):•	It is recommended that all users resort to the use of personal pseudonyms or nicknames with which to operate over the Internet, allowing them to have an authentic "digital identity" that does not compromise the security of their personal and professional lives.•	It is recommended that users take special care when publishing audiovisual and graphic content in their profiles, since in this case they may be placing the privacy and intimacy of people in their environment at risk.•	It is recommended to review and read, both in the moment prior to the user registration, and subsequently, the general conditions of use and the privacy policy that the platform makes available on their websites.•	It is recommended to adequately configure the degree of privacy of the user profile in the social network, so that it is not completely public, but only those people who have been catalogued as "friends" have access to the information published in the profile. "direct contacts" previously by the user.•	It is recommended to accept as a contact only those people known or with whom you have a previous relationship, not compulsively accepting all contact requests you receive and investigating whenever possible and necessary, who is the person requesting your contact through of the social network.•	It is recommended not to publish in the user profile physical contact information, which allows anyone to know where they live, where they work or study daily or the leisure places they usually frequent.•	To the users of micro blogging tools it is recommended to take special care regarding the publication of information relative to the places where they are at all times.•	It is recommended to use and publish only content with respect to which you have sufficient intellectual property rights. Otherwise, the user will be committing a civil offense protected by national courts.•	It is recommended that users use different user names and passwords to enter the different social networks of which they are members.•	It is recommended to use passwords with a minimum length of 8 characters, alphanumeric and with uppercase and lowercase letters.•	It is recommended that all users have installed and properly updated antivirus software on their computers.•	Minors should not reveal excessive personal data. Never give data to strangers.•	All the information concerning the website must be read. It explains who are the owners of the same and the purpose for which the data is requested.•	If the user is under fourteen years of age, the consent of the parent tutors is also needed. In these cases, whenever data is requested by a social network should ask the parents or guardians to see if they approve the subscription or not.•	The user names and password should not be communicated to third parties, nor shared among friends or classmates. These data are private and should not be communicated to third parties and / or strangers.•	Whenever there is any doubt regarding any situation that derives from the use of social networks and collaborating tools, parents or guardians should be asked.•	The computer must be kept in a common area of the house.•	Rules must be established on the use of the Internet at home.•	Parents should know the operation and possibilities of this type of platform, both positive and negative.•	Activate parental control and platform control tools, as well as establish parent or guardian mail as secondary contact email.•	Make sure that age verification controls are in place.•	Ensure the correct installation of the content blocker.•	Raise awareness and inform minors about aspects related to security.•	Explain to children that they should never meet people they have met in the online world and that if they do so, they should always be in the company of their parents or guardians.•	Ensure that children know the risks and implications of hosting content such as videos and photographs, as well as the use of webcams through social networks.•	Control the minor's user profile.•	Make sure that the child only accesses the pages recommended for their age.•	Make sure children do not use their full name.
Privacy Policy
